[{"question": "Grand Central Terminal, Park Avenue, New York is the world's", "options": ["A. largest railway station", "B. highest railway station", "C. longest railway station", "D. None of the above"], "answer": "A. largest railway station"}, {"question": "Entomology is the science that studies", "options": ["A. Behavior of human beings", "B. Medicine or Physiology", "C. Chemistry and Physics", "D. All the above"], "answer": "D. All the above"}, {"question": "Which state has Introduced new kin technology?", "options": ["A. Assam", "B. Delhi", "C. Haryana", "D. Punjab"], "answer": "D. Punjab"}, {"question": "Who has won pro Kabadi League this season?", "options": ["A. Dabang Delhi", "B. Bengal Warriors", "C. Puneri paltan", "D. U Mumba"], "answer": "B. Bengal Warriors"}, {"question": "First private train in India run between which of the two cities?", "options": ["A. Delhi-Lucknow", "B. Delhi-Ahmedabad", "C. Both of the above route", "D. None of the above"], "answer": "A. Delhi-Lucknow"}, {"question": "At the end of March 2019, what was the amount of India's external debt?", "options": ["A. US $ 540 billion", "B. US $ 543 billion", "C. US $ 547 billion", "D. US $ 541 billion"], "answer": "B. US $ 543 billion"}, {"question": "In which year was Sports Authority of India established?", "options": ["A. 1952", "B. 1967", "C. 1993", "D. 1982"], "answer": "D. 1982"}, {"question": "Headquater of International Olympic Committee is situated at?", "options": ["A. Athens", "B. Lausanne", "C. Dubai", "D. None of the above"], "answer": "B. Lausanne"}, {"question": "'The Coalition Years' is the autobiography of?", "options": ["A. L.K Advani", "B. Pranab Mukherjee", "C. Atal Behari Vajpayee", "D. Sonia Gandhi"], "answer": "B. Pranab Mukherjee"}, {"question": "Garampani Sanctuary is locate in which of the following places?", "options": ["A. Junagarh, Gujarat", "B. Kohima, Nagaland", "C. Diphu, Assam", "D. Gangtok, Sikkim"], "answer": "C. Diphu, Assam"}, {"question": "Entomology studies what?", "options": ["A. Behavior of human beings", "B. Insects", "C. The origin and history of technical and scientific terms", "D. The formation of rocks"], "answer": "B. Insects"}, {"question": "Galileo was an astronomer who", "options": ["A. Developed the telescope", "B. Discovered four satellites of Jupiter", "C. discovered that the movement of pendulum produces a regular time measurement", "D. All the above"], "answer": "B. Discovered four satellites of Jupiter"}, {"question": "Who is the father of geometry?", "options": ["A. Aristotle", "B. Euclid", "C. Pythagoras", "D. Kepler"], "answer": "B. Euclid"}, {"question": "Indian player Jude Felix is popular for which sports?", "options": ["A. Volleyball", "B. Football", "C. Hockey", "D. Tennis"], "answer": "C. Hockey"}, {"question": "Who is the current chief of the world bank group?", "options": ["A. Donald Tusk", "B. David Malpass", "C. Christine Lagarde", "D. Jim Yong Kim"], "answer": "B. David Malpass"}, {"question": "The Government of which state has instituted the 'Tansen Samman'?", "options": ["A. West Bengal", "B. Madhya Pradesh", "C. Bihar", "D. Gujrat"], "answer": "B. Madhya Pradesh"}, {"question": "Who was associated with the creation of pentium chip?", "options": ["A. Arun Netravalli", "B. Sabeer Bhatia", "C. Vinod Dham", "D. Vijay Dham"], "answer": "C. Vinod Dham"}, {"question": "Madhya Pradesh Chief Minister Kamal Nath has declared that Bhopal metro will be known as?", "options": ["A. Bhoj Metro", "B. Khoj Metro", "C. Bhopal Metro", "D. Auranga Metro"], "answer": "A. Bhoj Metro"}, {"question": "J.B. Dunlop is popular for which of the following inventions?", "options": ["A. Model airplanes", "B. Pneumatic rubber tire", "C. Rubber boot", "D. Automobile wheel rim"], "answer": "B. Pneumatic rubber tire"}, {"question": "What is the capital of India?", "options": ["A. Kolkata", "B. New Delhi", "C. Patna", "D. Kharagpur"], "answer": "B. New Delhi"}]